

### **ABOUT ME**

As a computer programmer and designer, I think my experience with the technical side could really help in the process of developing software. My goal is to provide programming solutions. So that it could be used in all products and all services and also bring entrepreneurship spirit to the team giving my passion and experience working as a start up."

#### LINKS

Linkedin : https://www.linkedin.com/in/wmn-nisal-a280651b6/

GitHub: https://github.com/wnsnisal

Web site: https://nisalhasindu.netlify.app/

#### PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of birth: 28/06/1992 Marital status: Single

### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Analytical and Problem-Solving Skills
- Project Management
- Creative thinking ability
- Leadership Skills
- Time Management
- Good Team Player
- Flexibility

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- C#, PHP, JavaScript/ NodeJs
- HTML / CSS / SCSS
- Solidity and web 3 technologies
- MS SQL, MySQL / Mongo dB
- Word press
- React js / Codeigniter 4 / Flutter
- Unity game development
- Git version control
- Bootstrap /Material UI
- Figma, Adobe XD, photoshop, illustrator

## NISAL HASINDU

WEB DEVELOPER



231/2, Dibulwala road, kattange, kahawatta.



+94740113411/+94702556391



wmnhasindu@gmail.com

### WORK EXPERIENCE

### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Logistics Blocks Limited c/o - BCS, Windsor House, Station Court, Station Road, Great Shelford, Cambridgeshire CB22 5NE, United Kingdom (Jun 2021 - Present).

· Gained experience in front end development

### INTERN SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

KYRAX SOLUTIONS - Thiriwanaketiya, Ratnapura. (Nov 2020 - Jun 2021)

• Gained experience in Full Stack Development with PHP and experience with wordpress CMS.

### MEDIA COORDINATOR

Sabaragamu maha saman dewalaya - Ratnapura.(Jan 2018 - Nov 2020)

• Gained experience events coordinator and graphic designing.

#### GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Monara Advertising - kuruvita.(Jan 2016 - Jan 2018)

• Gained experience in graphic designing and digital printing.

### PROJECT EXPERIENCES

# "ONLINE LIBRARY MANAGEMENT SYSTEM" web design and development assignment in HND

Developed a web-based Library management system for handling books details, users details and admin details.

TOOLS & TECHHNOLOGIES: PHP, MySQL, HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap

## "AYUBO DRIVE - VEHICLE RENT SYSTEM" HND - Programming assignment

Developed a Vehicle rent system (a desktop application) for renting vehicles and to calculate rent amounts and fees.

TOOLS & TECHNOLOGIES: Visual Studio IDE, C#, SQL

### "TRANSPORT MANAGEMENT SYSTEM" HND-Database assignment

A transport management system for handle delivering goods and handling transports.

TOOLS & TECHNOLOGIES: Visual Studio IDE, C#

### "REACT WEBSITES"

My portfolio website created using react js.

https://nisalhasindu.netlify.app/

### "WORDPRESS WEBSITES"

Developed 2 websites using wordpress cms for self study.

- <a href="http://drivingacademy.website/">http://drivingacademy.website/</a>
- <a href="http://printup.website/">http://printup.website/</a>

### NON RELATED REFEREES

Mr. P. Pavithra Piyumal Branch Manager ESOFT METRO COLLEGE – Ratnapura. No: 56/2, Bandaranayake Mawatha, Ratnapura.

Phone : (+94)77 310 1216 Email : piyumal@esoft.lk

Ms. D. Wickramaarchchi Retired Grama Niladari, Retired Grama Niladari – Muwagama Dayani, Aluketiya, Ratnapura. Phone: (+94)71 6081059

### **EDUCATION**

### HIRE NATIONAL DIPLOMA IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

ESOFT metro college - Ratnapura (2021) (Looking forward to the diploma award)

### GCE Advanced Level

R/Sivali Central College - Hidellana, Ratnapura (2013)

Done G.C.E Advanced Level Examination in meths stream with 1C pass.

### **COURSES**

## Diploma in Web engineering

ESOFT metro college - 2017

## Deploma in Mobile Application development with Kotlin

ESOFT metro college - 2021 to present

### **DECLARATION**

I hereby certify that the given particulars are true and accurate to the best of my knowledge.

W.M.Nisal Hasindu